##BLOCKS= 1
Note: 
Basic Endpoint Protocol

Use this protocol for endpoint assays that have unknowns that will have concentrations interpolated from a standard curve.  Modify the instrument setup for the wavelength(s) of interest for your assay.  You may also modify the template to include additional standards, unknowns, and controls.  To make modifications, click the plate section to make it active.

READER SUITABILITY:
SpectraMax M2, M2e, M3, M4, M5, and M5e.
SpectraMax Plus 384, 190, SpectraMax 190,  340PC 384 and VersaMax
Emax and Vmax


PROTOCOL REVISION HISTORY:
03/02/11 - Imported from 5.4 and edited.  (ELM)
10/11/11 - Updated with the additional instruments supported in SMP 6.1
~End 
Original Filename: 20230204_1309_THURS_B6_37; Date Last Saved: 2/4/2023 1:09:23 PM
